(Penny:)Sheldon, would you like to come in?
(Sheldon:)I suppose I could spare a few minutes.
[SHELDON GASPS]
(Sheldon:)Were you robbed?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)How can you be sure?
(Penny:)Sheldon, what do you want?
(Sheldon:)I'm certain this will come
as no surprise to you.
- Leonard is failing in another relationship.
- He's having problems with Stephanie?
(Sheldon:)She's sending virtual livestock
to random men on the Internet.
(Sheldon:)If I have any hope
of keeping them together, I need data.
(Sheldon:)Specifically, I need to know exactly
what Leonard did that caused you...
(Sheldon:)...to pop an emotional cap
in his buttocks.
(Penny:)- What?
- Again, urban slang.
(Sheldon:)In which I believe
I'm gaining remarkable fluency.
(Sheldon:)So, what is the down and the low?
(Sheldon:)And don't worry,
this is all entirely confidential...
(Sheldon:)...so you feel free to include any
and all shortcomings in the bedroom.